[
	{
		"question": "los calcetines",
		"answer": "socks"
	},
	{
		"question": "el calzoncillo",
		"answer": "under shorts"
	},
	{
		"question": "la corbata",
		"answer": "tie"
	},
	{
		"question": "los pantalones",
		"answer": "pants"
	},
	{
		"question": "los zapatos",
		"answer": "shoes"
	},
	{
		"question": "el árbol",
		"answer": "tree"
	},
	{
		"question": "la enredadera",
		"answer": "vine"
	},
	{
		"question": "la lagartija",
		"answer": "lizard"
	},
	{
		"question": "la libélula",
		"answer": "dragonfly"
	},
	{
		"question": "el mono",
		"answer": "monkey"
	}
]